YEVHENII MYNENKO

Front-end Developer

Kyiv • (063) 637-1765 • linkedin

githhub • portfilio • telegram • e-mail

About Me

I am a passionate and results-oriented Front-end Developer with nearly two years of experience in creating and maintaining intuitive, user-focused web applications.

Skills

Next, React JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Git, Prettier, Eslint, Github, Bitbucket, ES6+, Webpack, Gulp, SOLID, React Hooks, Formik, Tailwind, i18n, Zustand, Axios, TypeScript, React Query, Mobile First, CI/CD (basic) Service Worker (basic) GSAP,

Three js (basic), Shopify

Education

Bachelor's degree Sep 2022 – Present

National Technical University of Ukraine 'Kyiv Polytechnic Institute • Information systems and technologies

Soft Skills

• Ukraine: Native;

I worked in a team of up to 30 people.

• Russian: Native;

I have experience in managing a team, talking to a customer

• English: Intermediate

Experience

Front-end Developer

Mar 2023 – Present (as Mentor)

Ficeadvisor student portal • Volunteer • Student Council of the FICE

Remote

- Refactored code, conducted QA and leading the development team.
- Created new features, learned Zustand and improved interactions with backend developers.

Tech Stack: React, Next.js, Node.js, Zustand, MUI, StoryBook, SASS

Front-end Developer

CIE website • Volunteer • Student Council of the FICE

Mar 2023 – Present (as Mentor)
Remote

- Manage the development of the CMO website (in progress). I participated as a Team Lead.
- Built the project architecture, created tasks, managed the team, built communications with testers, designers, and backenders.

Tech Stack: React, Next.js, MUI, SASS

Front-end Developer

May 2024 - Jul 2024

UFN Website • Part time • EVDEV

Remote

- Created a user-friendly news portal using new web technologies.
- Built architecture to both client and backend.

Tech Stack: React, Next.js, SASS, Strapi

Front-end Developer

Jul 2024 - Sep 2024

Website and Admin panel • Full time • AMP Agency

Remote

- Worked on the website and admin panel
- Built communications with team.
- Participated in meetings in English.

Tech Stack: React, Next.js, SASS, Tailwind, Bitbucket